## SHERKHAN KHANSEIIT

# Full stack developer and QA engineer



Nur-Sultan

+7 707 225 8106 h.sherann@gmail.com/ h.sherann@mail.ru



https://sherkhan23.github.io/exceedlim



https://www.linkedin.com/in/sherkhan-khanseiit-b922641b9/

## Objective

I am a hardworking person with leadership qualities, I am a junior IT specialist, I always try to move on, I study fast and effectively, as well as a good team of employees. I have the desire and motivation to achieve my goals in the company. Also I just like to read books and program and extend my time usefully.

## **Additional Skills**

Program languages: C++, Python, JS, Java, PHP Web Dev: HTML, CSS, JS, PHP, Myadmin, BD Data base: SQl, PSQL, PHPmyAdmin Flexible team worker with leadership skills I study fast and try learn something useful Management skills, Computer skills Problem-solving, Public speaking

## Work Experience

2022.06 - current EurasianTech

### Full-stack engineer

- Laravel/ Php back-end
- Html/css/js/bootstrap front-end
- Git, GIt-lab, deploy
- Data-base: mySQL, PostgreSQL
- Making market places

2022.02 - current Documentolog

#### Software QA engineer

- Make test cases
- Work with CI/CD git
- Write automated code for websites
- Unit Testing/ Manual tests
- Software testing

2021.07 - 2022.06 Alem Educational System

### Web Developer and mentor of Web Development

- Make a training plan
- Conduct lectures
- Develop websites

Education

2019-2022 Astana IT University Bachelor of Computer Science

2008-2019 Gymnasium named by Karatai Turysov secondary education

4.5/5 GPA

Certifications	2022	Machine Learning Stanford University
	2020	Certified Linux Developer Linux foundation
	2017	Social Service volunteer
		Astana EXPO-2017

Languages KAZKAKH Native

Russian advanced

English Upper-intermediate (duolingo 110 = IELTS 6.5)

Arabic Writing, reading